All right, we are looking at the right
hand side of the screen at the agent.
And the first thing I'm going to ask you
to do is to hover over this area here
and drag it to the left because we want
a nice big display here because we are
going all in with our agent. Next up, if
you look here, uh this this is the model
that we're going to be using. If you
click here, I'm going to leave it in
auto mode. Auto mode, if you turn if I
turn off, you can see we can choose
different models. I'm going to leave it
in auto mode. It may be that that's all
that you have access to from the plan
that you're on. We're going to we're
going to let cursor decide what it wants
to do. Uh go into the unknown. All
right. And now over here in the agent
dropdown, I want you to select plan.
That means that we're putting the agent
into planning mode. And this is this is
going to be, I think, consistent with
all of the tools. We'll look at this
idea. Not all of them, almost all of
them. Uh we put it in plan mode. that's
gone a different color. It's now in
planning mode. And I'm just going to
type in here, uh, go ahead and plan. I
don't need to tell it what it's planning
because it will load agents.m MD into
context always by default. And you can
see stuff is happening. It's reading,
it's thinking, things are all happening.
While they're happening, move your mouse
down over here and have a look. You can
see that it's going to tell you in that
circular thing how much of the context
is used up, how much of the context
window has been consumed by the thinking
so far. And you can see that 6.4% has
been used. It also mentions that the
active rules, the things that it's
loaded in includes agents.md, which is
the file we've got. Excellent things are
happening. But more than that, we can
also see that it's created this document
here, the Camban MVP implementation
plan. And if you scroll down, you can
see that there's a whole lot of stuff
here. There's different phases. Phase
four, drag and drop. Phase five, add
cards. Phase six, phase, lots of phases.
Phase eight, and then there's an
architecture overview with some
diagramming here and some suggested
layout of scope and execution order. So
there's a whole lot of stuff in here
which is which is really interesting.
And of course the right thing to do now
is to work through this document, read
it carefully and be giving giving the
agent feedback on things on on where you
disagree and where you agree and so on.
But but but that's for boring people.
That's not what we're going to do. We're
just going to trust it. I'm not even
going to read it, but you probably
should. But I'm not going to. I'm just
going to go ahead and press the build
button here, which is saying I'm just
going to go right ahead and get started
with this. And off it goes. Now, because
I put it in yolo mode, it's just going
to go and do its thing. For you, you may
need be approving as you go and it will
be popping things up that you might need
to accept as they go. But things are all
happening for me. Files are appearing.
It's just created agit ignore. It's
created a frontend directory. stuff is
happening. Also, keep your eye on this
context used over here. It's now at
10.7%. You will see as things happen
that that that that context is being
used up. And look at look at all this.
I'm going to I'm going to make this a
bit bigger again. So, we we have this
front and center stuff is happening.
Watch it happening and enjoy this
process. Enjoy the sensation of having
your AI agent at work for you. So, for
me, it's now been going for for 5
minutes or so, and I have to say, I'm
enthralled. I've seen it like finding a
problem and fixing it. I've seen it
almost debating with itself about
things, watching this reasoning happen.
If you remember that that trick that
that that I I'd covered yesterday, it's
it's it's so interesting to see
everything happening. And uh and I'm
watching here, the context is now 28.8%.
You're probably seeing that, too. Keep
an eye on that. Keep an eye on
everything that's happening. Something
just failed there. Delete test fail. So,
it's running tests. It's seeing them
failing. It's coming back and fixing
them. This this is the the closest the
the the best way that I can show you
what an agent is. Remember, it's an LLM
in a loop with tools to achieve a goal.
And you can see all of those happening
right here in front of you. Okay. Okay.
It just finished. It claims it's run the
tests. And when it finished, this popped
up like it it actually launched it
itself. Now I' I've run this a couple of
times in the past and sometimes it
doesn't launch it itself. It just gives
you instructions. But in this case, it
has actually opened this up and run it
itself. And as it tells me at the end
here, it summarizes that all of the
phases are complete and it tells me what
I have to do now. I just simply have to
go to to look at this server myself
directly. It is running it says and that
is what we're going to do right now.
Okay. So, uh you may have needed to go
to bring up the terminal and do a cd
into front end and then do npm rundev.
And it should have told you exactly that
command, but it already ran that for me.
So, I don't need to do that. I'm now
going to go to to visit this and I know
that is running on localhost port 3000.
And bam, here it comes. First of all,
that's this is a camban. It has appeared
uh and it has like a backlog to-do in
progress review and done. And we can see
it there. Look, it's got the nice
highlighting. There is there is some
some node issue that it's complaining
about, but but we'll ignore that. Uh and
uh we I can see this little drag handles
right here. And uh I I'm I'm going to
try doing some drag and drop. So, I'm
going to click there. I'm going to drag
that over here and let go. And sure
enough, it moved over to that column.
Fair enough. Uh, I'm going to try adding
a card. Uh, this this is a card. And
this is its description. Let's see. Add.
And there we go. It's there. That's
great. Uh, it's uh um let's let's uh
let's try uh uh deleting a card. We'll
delete this one up here. Delete. And
it's gone. Wow. It is. It's working. And
we'll check that we can rename a column.
Let's uh not bad. We'll say not bad to
that column name. There we go. So, it
does appear to be meeting our
requirements. And this is this is for
this is like brought it up. I I didn't
give it any feedback. Now, it may not
have worked for you first time. It might
be janky. The one of these times I I
tried it actually didn't come up at all.
You simply have to give it the feedback.
Go back and say the following isn't
working. Um, and uh, you can see here
that this is uh, this is this is fine,
but but this is not it's a little bit
weird. Um, and uh, that that drag and
drop. And I also I don't think I can
move this down. Yeah, I can't re
reorganize here. And there's that issue
over there. So it's it's not perfect.
And so these are all things that we
could give it feedback to see how it
improves. So we can give it some
feedback. We can try that right now. I
can I can say uh um, it's it's uh,
mostly working. Nice. nicely. But next
JS is showing that there's one error red
symbol at the bottom
of the screen.
Also, the drag and drop
is a bit janky and it's not possible
to um reorder within a column.
Can this be made
more slick?
Uh, also it would be nice
to have more yellow
and purple on the screen.
Let's Let's say that. Let's give it a
few things, a little bit of feedback.
We'll let it go off and do its thought
and I'll see you back in a second when
it's had a stab at correcting for that.
Okay, so it has finished. It has
declared victory, I can see. But we'll
be the judge of that. Let's have a look
at it. Here it is. Okay, so first of
all, first of all, let's agree that it's
done a fine job with the colors. It's
definitely added some purple and yellow.
Congratulations to it. I can see that
that it has not succeeded in closing
this issue. Interestingly, I think it
did fix it while I was watching it and
and then and then it somehow has
reintroduced. I don't know. I don't know
how that happened. Um but the the issue
is still there and it's it's still the
same one. Um but this looks really nice
and and I note that that we can now we
can drag things over here and it will
come come into this box here and you can
now reorder them. I can move that up
which is really neat. So, it's all
working pretty well. Uh, just still got
this this issue here, but the look and
feel is great. You can now reorganize
within it. And I if if you're having a
similar experience, you can keep
hammering away with this issue. But as
far as I'm concerned, this is this is
good enough for cursor. It's done a fine
job. We have we've looked at writing
good agents.mmd and some of the tricks.
We've looked at putting it on yolo mode,
uh, running it, uh, giving it some
feedback and iterating, and we've, we've
just got a really good sense of what
it's like to work with the cursor agent
on building out a piece of software like
this canban project manager.